CHRIS AFAYOMIDE

Fullstack Developer

+234-8142360551 | daraseyi086@gmail.com | <u>https://seyi.vercel.app</u>

PROFILE

Fullstack developer with over 4 years experience.

I have successfully launched learning platforms, e-commerce sites, and blockchain projects I have worked as an intern, backend developer, frontend developer and as a fullstack developer for various organizations.

I love listening to music, working out, watching sitcoms, and most importantly, writing code. I enjoy solving problems and applying logic with creativity.

To have a more visual representation of my resume visit my portfolio https://seyi.vercel.app

WORK EXPERIENCE

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

Plusworld Roofing

<u>February 2022 - Present</u>

- I am helping to manage all the existing technical products of plusworld
- Similar to Udemy, I am building the web app for the Plusworld Academy learning platform to teach construction courses.
- You can view the deployed version here at https://plusworld.vercel.app
- I am using typescript, next.js for the frontend
- I am using postgres nodejs, aws for the backend and to store data.
- I helped to test and build the dandys beauty app, a child company of plusworld. available on playstore and apple store
- I started as an intern and was later made a permanent staff after three months for my unmatched work ethic
- https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.abby1.Dandys&pcampaignid=web_share

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER (PROJECT)

Afro Royals

November 2023 - Present (Project)

- I independently developed and designed from scratch a fully customizable web app to sell african fabrics
- I integrated a apayment system with the paystack api
- You can view the deployed version at https://afrifashion.vercel.app
- You can view the github repo at https://github.com/afayomide/afrifashion
- I worked on both the frontend and backend.
- I used javascript, react for the frontend
- I used mongo, nodejs, google cloud platform for the backend and to store data.

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER (PERSONAL PROJECT)

Audet Blog

August 2024 - Present (Personal Project)

- I independently developed and designed a fully customizable web app to upload and read music blogs
- You can view it here at https://audet.vercel.app
- You can view the github repo at https://github.com/afayomide/audet
- I worked on both the frontend and backend.
- I used typescript, next is for the frontend
- I used postgres, nodejs, google cloud, for the backend and to store data.

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER (PERSONAL PROJECT)

AdotAdvisor

september 2023 - October 2023

- I Independently developed and designed from scratch a fully customizable web app to give information on the stock market
- You can view it here at https://adotadvisor.vercel.app
- You can view the github repo at https://github.com/afayomide/adotadvisor
- I worked on both the frontend and backend.
- I also built the mobile app version
- You can view the github repo at https://github.com/afayomide/adotadvisorapp
- I used javascript, React for the frontend
- I used mongo, nodejs, for the backend and to store data.

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

alphasniffer

June 2023 - August 2023

- I singlehandedly built and designed from scratch a fully customizable web app for the launch of a crypto project
- I worked on both the frontend
- I used javascript, React for the frontend

OTHER OLDER PROJECTS

scentsbyfolak : https://scentsbyfolak.vercel.app/

Mksignature : https://mksignature-afayomide.vercel.app/

Youtubemusic : https://youtubemusic-nu.vercel.app

EDUCATION

Course

2024

Harvard Computer Science - CS50

Course

2021

Udemy - Fullstack Development course https://www.udemy.com/certificate/UC-ae070ffc-8e29-4436-b853-409ad816eeb1/

Course

2024

Univeristy at buffalo - Blockchain/Dapps

https://coursera.org/verify/UGQZG8RNAAB9

Course

2022

META|FACEBOOK - Frontend Developer

https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/specialization/certificate/8C8DHXPZX4AD

University

2023

Ekiti state University - Physiology

PRIMARY SKILLS

- Javascript
- Typescript
- Nextjs
- React && React Native
- SASS
- node.js Express
- postgreSQL
- mongo
- bootstrap
- aws (cloud storage)
- tailwind
- Git && Github

SECONDARY SKILLS

- vueis
- nestjs
- tailwind
- Linux
- · email administrator

REFERENCE

Project Manager && SCRUM MASTER

- Plusworld Academy

nAOMI ANEZU

+234 907 208 7522 - naomianezu@gmail.com